To start this Spring Boot project, make sure you have installed JDK 8 and Maven.
After importing the project into the IDE, run the main method in VSApplication.java to start the application.

In addition to this, I also packaged the jar package for you, you can find the VBB-2.2.5.jar package
in the /target directory and run the project on linux directly using the following commands:

nohup java -jar  VBB-2.2.5.jar >testLog.log 2>&1 &